[
    {
        "id":1,
        "question":"What JVM stands for",
        "1":"JAVA variable Manager",
        "2":"JAVA Virtual Machine",
        "3":"JAVA Virtual manager",
        "4":"java variable machine",
        "answer":"2"
    },
    {
        "id":2,
        "question":"Whay is multiple inheritance not supported in java",
        "1":"JAVA supports multiple inheritance",
        "2":"because of the diamond problem",
        "3":"uses mixing instead",
        "4":"for managing memory",
        "answer":"2"
    },
    {
        "id":3,
        "question":"What is inheritance",
        "1":"hiding data",
        "2":"Reusing methods",
        "3":"To inherit super class properties in  child class",
        "4":"recursion",
        "answer":"3"
    },
    {
        "id":4,
        "question":"How can an object become serializable",
        "1":"it is not possible",
        "2":"A class has to extend serializable",
        "3":"Every object is serializable ",
        "4":"when a class or super class extend serializable",
        "answer":"4"
    },
    {
        "id":5,
        "question":"Which expression is thrown when java is out of memory",
        "1":"FullMemoryException",
        "2":"OutOfMemoryError",
        "3":"FullStackException",
        "4":"jOutOfSpaceException",
        "answer":"2"
    },
    {
        "id":6,
        "question":"What JVM stands for",
        "1":"JAVA variable Manager",
        "2":"JAVA Virtual Machine",
        "3":"JAVA Virtual manager",
        "4":"java variable machine",
        "answer":"2"
    },
    {
        "id":7,
        "question":"Which expression is thrown when java is out of memory",
        "1":"FullMemoryException",
        "2":"OutOfMemoryError",
        "3":"FullStackException",
        "4":"jOutOfSpaceException",
        "answer":"2"
    },
    {

        "id":8,
        "question":"How can an object become serializable",
        "1":"it is not possible",
        "2":"A class has to extend serializable",
        "3":"Every object is serializable ",
        "4":"when a class or super class extend serializable",
        "answer":"4"
    },
    {

        "id":9,
        "question":"What JVM stands for",
        "1":"JAVA variable Manager",
        "2":"JAVA Virtual Machine",
        "3":"JAVA Virtual manager",
        "4":"java variable machine",
        "answer":"2"
    },
    {

        "id":10,
        "question":"How can an object become serializable",
        "1":"it is not possible",
        "2":"A class has to extend serializable",
        "3":"Every object is serializable ",
        "4":"when a class or super class extend serializable",
        "answer":"4"
    }

]